Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Storm performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1100; Storm plays the electric bass guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Storm performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1101; Storm plays the electric bass guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Bléz performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1102; Bléz performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1103; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1104; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1105; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1106; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1107; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1108; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Genny Jam backstage at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1109; Genny Jam kicks open the door backstage during BE'LA DONA performance at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Bléz backstage at Fillmore Silver Spring, 2012-11-29; 199chippy_1110; Bléz prepares for performance with BE'LA DONA backstage at Fillmore Silver Spring.
  - Ice performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0918; Ice plays guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0919; Greg Boyer plays trombone while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0920; Sweet Cherie snaps her fingers and dances while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Peekaso and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0921; KK stands at a microphone while performing with Chuck Brown Band. In the foreground Peekaso paints on stage.
  - Wiley Brown and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0922; From left to right siblings Wiley Brown and KK sing together while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Other musicians are visible in the background.
  - Peekaso painting with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0923; Peekaso paints on stage while performing with Chuck Brown Band. He holds a tablet in his left hand and a paintbrush in his right hand.
  - Wiley Brown and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0924; From left to right siblings Wiley Brown and KK sing together while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Other musicians are visible in the background.
  - KK, Wiley Brown, D. Floyd, and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0925; From left to right siblings KK and Wiley Brown sing, Greg Boyer plays trombone, and D. Floyd dances while performing with Chuck Brown Band. To the far right a musician is visible.
  - Mighty Moe performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0926; Mighty Moe plays drums while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Wiley Brown and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0927; From left to right siblings Wiley Brown and KK sing together while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Sweet Cherie is visible in the background along with a guitar player. Peekaso is visible to the right painting on stage.
  - Wiley Brown and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0928; From left to right siblings Wiley Brown and KK sing together while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Peekaso is visible to the right painting on stage.
  - Wiley Brown and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0929; From right to left siblings Wiley Brown and KK sing together while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0930; Greg Boyer dances and holds a trombone while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Congas and Sweet Cherie on keys are visible in the background.
  - D. Floyd and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0931; D. Floyd holds a microphone in his right hand and sings while Greg Boyer flexes his arm and holds a trombone during a performance with Chuck Brown Band.
  - D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0932; D. Floyd holds his arms up and signs while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Other musicians are visible to the right.
  - Bryan Mills performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0933; Bryan Mills holds a saxophone while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Other musicians are visible behind him.
  - Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0934; Greg Boyer hold his arms up while performing with Chuck Brown Band. He holds a trombone in his left hand.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing with Ledisi at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-03; 199chippy_0935; D. Floyd and Ledisi perform with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. From left to right: Mighty Mo, Frank 'Scooby' Sirius, Ledisi, Kwick Foot, KK (sitting), D. Floyd, Greg Boyer, Ice, and Brad Clements. Keyboard player is unidentified. Fans can be seen in the audience.
  - Another Sound performing at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0822; Musicians from Another Sound perform on stage. Fans is silhouetted against the stage.
  - Genny Jam and Mighty Moe performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0823; From left to right Genny Jam plays guitar and Mighty Moe plays congas while performing with BE'LA DONA.
  - Bléz and Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0824; From left to right Bléz and Sugar Rai play Tambourines and dance while performing with BE'LA DONA.
  - Geronimo on cowbell performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0825; Geronimo plays cowbell backstage while performing with BE'LA DONA.
  - Bléz and Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0826; From left to right Bléz and Sugar Rai sing while performing with BE'LA DONA. The audience is visible to the right.
  - D. Floyd performing with Still Familiar at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0827; D. Floyd holds and microphone in his hands and signs while performing with Still Familiar. Another performer is visible in the background.
  - Ms Kim performing with Still Familiar at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-06; 199chippy_0828; Ms Kim holds a microphone in her right hand and signs while performing with Still Familiar.
  - Shannon Browne performs with BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1116; Shannon Browne performs with BE'LA DONA for 2012 Go-Go Christmas at the Howard theater.
  - BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1117; BE'LA DONA perform for 2012 Go-Go Christmas at the Howard theater.
  - BE'LA DONA's front line performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1118; BE'LA DONA's front line performs for 2012 Go-Go Christmas at the Howard theater.
  - BE'LA DONA's front line performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1119; BE'LA DONA's front line performs for 2012 Go-Go Christmas at the Howard theater.
  - BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1120; BE'LA DONA performing at the Howard Theatre. The event like is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1121; Sugar Rai dances while playing a tambourine. Bléz can also be seen playing a tambourine. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1122; Miss Karis dances while playing the tambourine. Sugar Rai is visible in the background dancing while playing tambourine. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1123; Miss Karis dances while playing the tambourine. Sugar Rai is visible in the background dancing while playing tambourine. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - BE'LA DONA performing during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1124; Miss Karis dances while playing the tambourine. Sugar Rai is visible in the background dancing while playing tambourine. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1125; Miss Karis dances while playing the tambourine. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Genny Jam performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1126; Genny Jam is playing guitar with BE'LA DONA at the Howard Theatre. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1127; Sugar Rai plays the tambourine and dances while performing with BE'LA DONA. This event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - Genny Jam performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1128; Genny Jam and Storm can be seen playing guitar with BE'LA DONA. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Shannon Browne performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1129; Shannon Browne plays drums performing with BE'LA DONA. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1130; Kwick Foot sits at a drum set during his performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. He is wearing a Washington Redskins Santa Claus hat and beaded necklace. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1131; Kwick Foot poses for a photograph during his performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. He is wearing a Washington Redskins Santa Claus hat. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Kwick Foot and Mighty Moe performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1132; Kwick Foot and Mighty Moe playing drums and congas respectively during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1133; Sweet Cherie stands at the microphone during a performance with the BE'LA DONA at the Howard Theatre. She is wearing a Santa Claus hat. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Genny Jam and Sugar Rai backstage at the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1134; Genny Jam and Sugar Rai backstage at the Howard Theatre preparing for their performance with BE'LA DONA. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with BE'LA DONA during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1135; Sweet Cherie makes a expressive face and poses for a photograph during a performance with BE'LA DONA at the Howard Theatre. She is wearing a Santa Claus hat. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - Peekaso live art exhibit at the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1136; Peekaso conducts a live art exhibit at the Howard Theatre during a concert. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - KK and Wiley Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1137; KK and Wiley Brown sing together during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre.
  - Buggs performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1138; Buggs smiles during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas Concert.
  - Buggs performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1139; Buggs leans back and tosses his hand in the air during his performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas Concert.
  - Peekaso live art exhibit during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1140; Peekaso conducts a live art exhibit at the Howard Theatre during a concert. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1141; Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. He is wearing a Washington Redskins Santa Claus hat. This event is the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre.
  - Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1142; Greg Boyer checks his watch during a performance with Chuck Brown Band. It's likely a reference to the Rare Essence song 'Do you know what time it is?'. Sugar Rai. Buggs, and other musicians can be seen in the background. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - BE'LA DONA and Chuck Brown Band performing together during the 2012 Go-Go Christmas at Howard Theatre, 2012-12-17; 199chippy_1143; BE'LA DONA and Chuck Brown Band performing together at the Howard Theatre. The event is likely a Go-Go Christmas concert.
  - Kool Keys performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0872; Kool Keys plays the keys with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - BE'LA DONA performs at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0873; From left to right Bléz, Sugar Rai, and Miss Karis sing during a BE'LA DONA performance. Behind them Sweet Cherie on keys, Storm on electric bass, Shannon Browne on drums, Genny Jam on electric guitar, and an unknown keys player are visible.
  - BE'LA DONA performs at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0874; From left to right Bléz, Sugar Rai, and Miss Karis sing during a BE'LA DONA performance. Behind them Sweet Cherie on keys, Storm on electric bass, Shannon Browne on drums, Genny Jam on electric guitar, and Kool Keys are visible in the background.
  - Bléz and Sugar Rai perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0875; Bléz Coe and Sugar Rai perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Bléz, Sugar Rai, and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0876; Bléz Coe, Sugar Rai, and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Bléz, Sugar Rai, and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0877; Bléz Coe, Sugar Rai, and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Ms Kim and D. Floyd perform with Still Familiar at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0878; Ms Kim and D. Floyd perform with Still Familiar at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-20; 199chippy_0879; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Balloons fall on New Year's Eve at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1159; Balloon drop at La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve.
  - Ju-Ju poses dances at La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1161; Ju-Ju dances while holding a drink in his right hand.
  - Ju-Ju performs with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1162; Juju playing the drums during a performance with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue. An unidentified person can be seen in the background playing roto toms.
  - Junie performing with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1163; Junie plays electric guitar with E. U. On New Year's Eve at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Ju-Ju performing with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1164; Juju playing the drums during a performance with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue. An unidentified person can be seen in the background playing roto toms,.
  - Sugar Bear and Junie performing with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1165; Sugar Bear and Junie play guitars together on stage with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue. Sugar Bear looks at Junie as he plays.
  - Sugar Bear performs with E. U. At La Fontaine Bleue on New Year's Eve, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1166; Sugar Bear performs with E. U. Front man plays guitar while band mates play both keyboards and drums in the background. Up close shot of drumsticks.
  - Fan dances along with fans during Rare Essence performance at Love Night Club, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1167; Excited fans dance at Love Night Club. Main focus on fan in pink zebra print dress with bangles on her left arm.
  - Tray Chaney performing with DC Vybe at La Fontaine Bleue, 2012-12-31; 199chippy_1223; Tray Chaney smiles and points while performing with DC Vybe. Songbird is visible in the background.
  - D. P. Performing with Still Familiar, 2013; 199chippy_1424; D. P. Plays the Mellophone while performing with Still Familiar at a cookout.
  - D. Floyd and a fan dance with Still Familiar, 2013; 199chippy_1425; D. Floyd and a fan can be seen dancing on stage during an outdoor performance with Still Familiar.
  - Ms Kim celebrating her birthday at Fusion Grill, 2013; 199chippy_1426; Ms Kim smiling while sitting at the bar at Fusion Grill. Two beverage sit in the foreground on the bar.
  - Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013; 199chippy_1435; Go-Go fan from North Carolina poses with a musician.
  - KK with Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1436; KK posing with Go-Go fan from North Carolina..
  - KeKe with Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1437; KeKe posing with Go-Go fan from North Carolina..
  - D. Floyd with Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1438; D. Floyd posing with Go-Go fan from North Carolina..
  - Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1439; A Go-Go fan from North Carolina plays the congas and bongos.
  - Miss Loretta and Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1440; A Go-Go fan from North Carolina with Miss Loretta Simms (right) and an unidentified woman..
  - Chip Py and Miss Loretta with Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1441; From left to right Miss Loretta Sims, Chip Py, and an unidentified Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge.
  - Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1442; From right to left Miss Loretta Sims and two unidentified Go-Go fans from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge.
  - Go-Go Mickey and Go-Go fan from North Carolina at Martini's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1443; Go-Go fan from North Carolina posing with Go-Go Mickey.
  - Deidra Love performing with Red Carpet Affair Band at Eclipse Nightclub, 2013-02-13; 199chippy_1444; Deidra Love holding microphone in right hand and pointing her left hand while performing with Red Carpet Affair Band at Eclipse Nightclub.
  - Still Familiar performs at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-03; 199chippy_1405; Quisy and Ms Kim perform at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge.
  - Quisy with Still Familiar performing at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-03; 199chippy_1406; Quisy performing at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge. Band mate plays drums in the background.
  - Quisy, Ms Kim and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go perform with Still Familiar at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-03; 199chippy_1407; Quisy, Ms Kim and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go perform with Still Familiar at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge.
  - Still Familiar at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-03; 199chippy_1408; D. Floyd, Ms Kim, and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go perform with Still Familiar. Fans and band members are all looking to the right.
  - Ms Kim, Quisy, Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and Still Familiar perform at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-03; 199chippy_1409; Ms Kim, Quisy, Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and Still Familiar perform on stage at Twelve Restaurant and Lounge. A band member stands up front with them while playing saxophone.
  - Still Familiar performs at Martin's Restaurant and Lounge, 2013-03; 199chippy_1410; From right to left Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go, Ms Kim, D. Floyd, Go-Go Mickey, and Kwick Foot on the drum set perform on stage for a live audience at Martin's Restaurant and Lounge. Band members back them up on drums and guitar. Band mate plays trumpet next to them, but just out of frame.
  - Sweet Cherie performs with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1343; Sweet Cherie performs with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre.
  - Sweet Cherie performs with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1344; Sweet Cherie performs with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre.
  - Kwick Foot and Ice perform with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1345; Kwick Foot and bass player Ice perform with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre.
  - Mighty Moe performs with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1346; Mighty Moe plays the bongos and congas while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Band mate plays keyboards in the background.
  - Mighty Moe performs with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1347; Mighty Moe plays the bongos and congas while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Band mate plays keyboards in the background.
  - KK performs with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1348; KK performs with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre. Band mate plays guitar in the background.
  - Dwele, Sweet Cherie and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go perform with Chuck Brown Band at Howard Theatre, 2013-03-17; 199chippy_1349; Dwele, Sweet Cherie and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go perform with Chuck Brown Band at the Howard Theatre.